uringed.com 2010-11-29

# uRinged - Free Mobile Content Sharing!!

_uRinged Privacy Notice_

This policy document describes how uRinged and its subsidiaries and affiliates treat your personal information that you provide in connection with creating and maintaining an account with uRinged or when you use uRinged Services. This policy describes what information we may collect and how we use such information. By accepting the terms of use at the time of registration, you explicitly agree to uRinged's use and disclosure to your personal information as described in this document. 

**Personal Information**

uRinged collects only the personal information from you that are necessary in connection with your use of uRinged web sites (collectively "uRinged Portal") and the services. We do not collect, share or use your personal information in any other way except mentioned in this document. 

**Account Related Information**

Certain activity on the uRinged website requires you to have a valid uRinged account. We ask for some personal information when you create a uRinged account, including your mobile phone number, valid email address and password to create a protected identity for yourself on uRinged web site. We may also ask you to provide further validation information such as your address, city and zip code in order for us to provide you with the services that you require. When you perform certain transactions on uRinged you may be asked to fill an electronic or paper form to provide Credit Card or Bank Details. 

**Use of Information**

**Transaction Processing:** We may share your bank details and credit card information in a secure manner to third party payment providers and/or banks. We may also share your user-id and/or mobile phone number to process a transaction and/or deliver content to you. 

**Content uploaded on the site:** Any personal information or content that you post on uRinged Portals or voluntarily disclose online becomes publicly available and can be used by others. 

**Other Usage:** We may record information about your usage on uRinged, such as your how you use certain services, your preferences, types of content you download and frequency and size of such downloads as well as your browsing behavior.We may also save this information separately and associate this with your account. 

**Use of Cookies and other non personal information**

We may use your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally identifiable information such as cookies, IP addresses, browser type etc. to improve the quality of the sites and create new features by storing, tracking and analyzing User preferences and trends. We may use cookies to store information so that your visit to our Portal is seamless and provide custom, personalized content and information to you. We may further use cookies and java scripts to aggregate certain metrics such as page views etc. and track you're your entries. 

**Links to Other Sites**

Pages on our Portal may contain links to other sites. uRinged is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites and encourage you to read the privacy statement on each website (if available) you visit through a link provided to you from us.

**Customer Service Related Information**

You may be able to send us correspondence, including e-mails, phone calls, web based forms and SMS or using any other means available to you. You agree that we may retain such information in the records of your account. We may also retain customer service correspondences made to you and your responses. We do that to improve our customer service, track the issues that our users may have collectively and to investigate violations to our terms of use.

**Sharing your personal data**

uRinged will not sell or rent your personal information to other for marketing purposes, however we may use your personal information to verify your identity, request third parties to perform additional verification to help us authenticating your account and ensuring accuracy of the information that you may provide to us. We will only share the necessary information to assist us with verification. We may share your personal information wherever it is required by law or needed by law enforcement authorities. 

**Security**

All access to the data displayed on uRinged Portal is secured by using a unique username and password. Our employee may have access to your data on strict compliance basis and we have process in place to manage access to such information whenever it is necessary. We make reasonable efforts to ensure security throughout our systems, however cannot guarantee that your personal information may not be compromised, accessed, disclosed, altered or deleted by breach of a technical, managerial or administrative process. We may post a notice to this web site or send you an e-mail if such an event to occur. 

**Storage of Data**

We have several systems located throughout the world and your personal information can be stored and processed in anyone of these locations. You agree and consent to the transfer and processing of your personal information in any of the location uRinged system may be located in or is technically feasible for uRinged. 

**Transfer of Data**

In event of a merger with another company or sale to another company or winding up or bankruptcy, your information that we have may be transferred except to the extend the law may prohibit. 

**Notification of Changes**

We may continue to post update and changes to this privacy policy from time to time and will make reasonable efforts to inform you of the changes. We encourage you to review this document on the web site periodically. You continued use of the uRinged sites, portals and/or services constitutes your agreement to our Privacy Statement and any updates to it. 

**Contacting uRinged**

If you have a privacy concern or questions regarding this policy you can write to [privacy@uringed.com](mailto:privacy@uringed.com). 

**Effective Date:**
